Downloaded from YTS.MX
Modify by Blue-Bird™
Stay down!
Don't move!
Yeah!
Mayday! Mayday!
This is the Sawyer-Two.
We're under attack by pirates.
Requesting an immediate aid.
They say everybody's
good at something.
Me? I talk to fish.
That's how I met
my friend, Storm.
He's always there
when I need a lift.
Some people
think that makes me a joke.
But I don't care.
You know why?
'Cause I'm also good
at something else.
And that's breaking heads.
Pow! Papa took on
all the pirates.
I was like,
"Well, the pirates
think that--"
- Hi-ya!
Papa kicked their butts.
Those chum lickers
didn't stand a chance.
Ooh!
Papa kicked their asses
and took their names.
Yeah! Come on!
- Watch out.
Sorry, Pops. My bad.
Oh, yeah,
this is my son, Arthur Jr.
See, four years ago,
everything changed.
I met a woman, fell in love,
and the next thing I know,
we're getting married
and having a kid.
This little guy's
the best thing
that ever happened to me.
But this kid,
he doesn't sleep.
What you got in there, huh?
Okay--
And he never misses.
- What the...
And then,
I'm up at the crack of dawn
because on top of getting
married and having a kid...
- ...I finally got a job.
That's right.
I'm the king
of freaking Atlantis.
- How did I score that,
you asked?
Well, I stopped
my brother, Orm,
from attacking
the surface world.
And in doing so,
I claimed the throne from him.
At first I was all like...
Yeah!
The territorial waters
are long held...
But then,
as it turned out,
being king wasn't all
it was cracked up to be.
It's just meetings
all day and politics.
I'm so bored,
I don't even know
which end of the Brine King
I'm supposed to be looking at
half the time.
Whoo!
Yeah! That was awesome!
And if
that's not bad enough,
turns out there's this whole
Council of Houses thing
that nobody told me about.
Which basically gets to shoot
down everything I want to do.
The only thing
that makes all the hard work
and sleepless nights worthwhile
is hanging with my little man.
Hey! You missed me!
But of course,
there are fun parts of the job.
Whoa!
I get
to keep the sea safe
the best way I know how.
Especially
when I get to take down
an illegal cage fight or two.
But for everything I get right,
something else gets screwed up.
Ah, fu--
♪ Born to be wild ♪
- Oh, yeah.
- Here you go.
Slainte.
So...
he's gonna need
a little brother or sister
to play with.
He's got a dog.
Hey, I'm serious.
I saw how lonely it was
for you growing up.
An only child.
I always regretted
I couldn't give you that.
Yeah, well,
don't be too hard on yourself.
Turns out I have a brother
and he's a total dick bag.
Come on.
Your relationship with Orm
isn't how it usually is.
Sure, siblings bicker
and fight...
but at the end of the day,
they're family.
You should be able
to count on them for help.
Yeah, well, I'll still take
the dog over him any day.
Hey, look at that.
Holy crap.
Hi, baby boy.
Are you talking
to the fishies?
Oh, man.
Pops, this is blowing my mind.
My whole life I've wanted
to share this gift
with someone.
Yeah, but you and me, son,
we're different.
We're special.
We're connected
to the land and the sea.
I can't wait to introduce you
to all the majestic creatures
on our planet.
And show you how awesome
this world can be.
Yeah, you and me.
I cross-referenced
the coordinates from Dr. Shin.
Nothing.
Still no sign
of Atlantean remnants
under the ice.
Looks like he's led us
on another wild goose chase.
Every day I don't fix
my power suit
is another day Aquaman
gets to live.
Check again.
We're close this time.
I can feel it.
Expedition log day 463,
Dr. Stephen Shin recording.
My quest for Atlantis
has brought me
to the ends of the earth.
David Kane
is losing his patience.
If I don't turn up
the Atlantean technology
he's looking for soon,
they're probably going to...
um...
You know what,
let's not even go there.
I'm sure everything
will be fine.
Dr. Shin, take a look at this.
Please tell me
you found something.
Seismic array is going crazy.
Where's the epicenter?
We're standing on it.
- Run!
What just happened?
An earthquake?
No. I think it was a piece
of ice sheet breaking off.
Come on. Get up.
- I think I broke my ankle!
- Come on. Let's go!
Come on, get up.
Go, we gotta go! We gotta go!
Come on, we gotta move!
Come on!
Please, please. No, no!
Help, please! Don't let go!
What the hell happened to you?
There's something back there.
Astounding.
My readings show
something's down here.
And it's definitely big enough
to be an Atlantean ship.
If it is, we might be able
to scavenge the tech you need
to fix your suit.
How is this place
even possible?
This was all probably solid ice
until we started
heating the planet.
Well, thank God
for global warming, am I right?
Uh, yeah,
that's not exactly
a good thing.
The tracks lead down there.
Suit up.
Wait. The tracks lead
down there, which means...
the monster's down there.
Okay. I guess
we're going down there.
I don't believe this.
It's a structure of some kind.
And there's more buried
in the ice.
Here I thought we were
just going to find a ship.
- Everyone,
fan out and search.
- Yes, sir.
We've stumbled upon
something big here, doc.
This has to be
a few thousand years old.
Astounding.
Whoa.
Uh...
Ow...
What is this place?
At last, you are here.
Free me from my prison
and I will grant you
the strength
to kill the man
who murdered your father.
You can't leave him like this!
You ask the sea for mercy.
Get out of here!
You need to live
so you can kill
that son of a bitch!
You will take from him
what he stole from you.
His home will burn
and his kingdom will fall
before my legions.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
David. No, David.
David! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
David. David, it's okay.
You're all right.
What the hell is that thing?
...Just unbelievable footage
coming in
from all around the world.
Good evening, folks.
In the past five months,
we've seen an extraordinary
rise in temperatures
reported around the world.
And that has resulted
in some of the wildest weather
we've ever seen.
Yes, this is thundersnow
in Dallas, Texas.
- Visibility is near zero...
...and there's more snow
expected tonight
than Dallas usually sees
in an entire year.
It's only one part of
a worldwide weather phenomenon
unlike anything
we've ever seen before.
Arthur.
The Council's called
for an emergency gathering.
There's been
another plague outbreak.
...scientists are
at a loss to explain.
But the real question is,
how long will it continue?
And how much hotter
is it going to get?
Where did it hit this time?
The Ninth Tride of Atlantis,
and there are now reports
of outbreaks
in the Fishermen Kingdom
as well.
There haven't been outbreaks
like this in centuries.
Why now?
Increased ocean acidity,
decreased oxygen levels,
toxic algal blooms.
Take your pick.
The surface has been
poisoning our atmosphere
for over a century.
You can't expect them to care
about what happens to us
if they don't even know
we exist.
If you want to be a part
of the conversation,
we have to take our seat
at the table.
It's time for Atlantis
to reveal itself
to the surface.
Your majesty is well aware
of the Council's position
on this.
Listen, we can talk
to their scientists
and combine our technologies
to reverse the damage
that they've already done.
And I know this is
against our traditions,
but the world is shrinking,
and the old ways aren't gonna
protect us anymore.
Times have changed.
Atlantis wants this.
There's a whole generation
out there
that don't want
to hide anymore.
Have you already forgotten
that this plague
killed your own beloved mentor,
and you want to negotiate
with them?
We gave your brother war powers
and made him Ocean Master
for a reason.
If we ever decide
to make ourselves known
to the surface-dwellers,
it will be to eradicate them,
not to co-exist.
Hey, not bad.
Used to take me twice as long
to get you to go to sleep.
I don't know
how you did it, Pops.
Mera and I have
the whole kingdom helping us,
but that little baby boy
is still kicking our asses.
And you...
taking care of me,
raising me on your own...
You're the real superhero.
- To single parents.
- Mmm.
Well, my job was a little less
stressful than yours.
Yeah, well,
I just plain suck at my job.
Vulko told me to bring
the land and the sea together.
The problem is
half of Atlantis still
wants to destroy the surface.
They won't listen.
I can't bring shit together.
Vulko believed in you. Aye.
I know.
I miss him.
Hey.
You can't save them all, son.
You really want to know how
I raised you here by myself?
I just kept going.
You celebrate the wins,
you mourn the losses.
And you wake up the next day
and you do it again.
Sometimes not giving up
is the most heroic thing
you can do.
Humans were not made
to live at these depths.
Yeah, don't worry about that.
You just remember
who built this ship.
I'm more worried about
how long ago they built it.
We're coming up on it.
Engage stealth mode.
Hey, doc.
You stand ready
with that big gun of yours.
Expedition log, day 613.
Kane is off on our most
dangerous mission yet.
A three man
octobot infiltration team.
It's incredible
that these ancient machines
we found
still function
after all these years.
All I did was retrofit them
to our needs.
But they require
a very specialized fuel
to keep them running.
Kane calls it orichalcum.
I don't know how
he knows about this,
but it all started the day
he found that trident.
Suddenly, he knows secrets
that he couldn't possibly know,
including the only way
to obtain this orichalcum
is to steal it
from highly-protected
storage vaults.
And we're about to hit the most
dangerous one of them all.
Okay, you have 15 minutes
to get in and out.
No margin for error.
Yeah, this should
take you through.
We don't want
any confrontation.
David, we can't fight
their entire army.
Stay vigilant.
We have no idea
what kind of security measures
they have down there.
Commencing extraction.
Be careful.
It's highly volatile.
Loading barge now.
Stingray, change of plans.
I need an extraction now!
- All hands to battle stations.
Astounding.
Attention, unidentified vessel.
You are out
of the transit zone.
Doctor, power up
the sonic battery.
Illegal border crossing
will be met with deadly force.
Now!
Commencing charge.
Border Control,
intruder approaching.
Arm hydro cannon
and lock target.
Hydro cannon
at front border gate
locking in on target.
Chargers set
to maximum power.
Intruder in sight.
Take them out!
What are you waiting for?
Fire!
Sir, Atlantean hostiles
are approaching.
Split up.
Make your way
to the extraction point.
Roger.
They've raided
the storage vault.
We can't let them get away.
Don't worry, they won't.
I'm on this one.
Hold your fire!
They're cutting
through the Night Market.
Watch out for the civilians.
Warning. Warning.
Illegal entrance
into hypertube.
Exceeding maximum speed
of 600 knots.
Reduce speed immediately.
Oh, shit.
David, we're here
at the extraction point.
The orichalcum is onboard
and secure.
Come on, let's go!
Not yet!
I'm gonna kill me
a dead mermaid.
Get away from my wife!
Your wife?
First you steal
your brother's throne,
then you steal his woman?
Aquaman, shame on you.
Uh, David, we gotta go.
The entire Atlantean army
is headed this way.
If we don't leave now,
we're dead.
Twenty degrees port!
Fire the sonic cannon!
Come on, Shin!
Lady Karshon has called
an emergency session
of the High Council
to discuss a motion
that would strip the throne
of its executive power.
The throne
is the heart of Atlantis.
Too often now it stands empty,
while our king spends half
his time on land.
And now his
surface world enemies
have followed him home.
This tragedy is merely
a taste
of the havoc
that will be wrought,
if Atlantis ever becomes known
to the surface.
Because if he cannot protect
his own family,
how is he supposed
to protect us?
He's different now.
He's stronger than before.
And he can fight me
without the power suit.
And where the hell did he get
all the new toys from?
The technology seems ancient,
but we've never seen
anything like it.
That weapon he used fires
some kind of ultrasonic energy
that disrupts
the nervous system.
Do we know what was stolen?
He escaped with a large
stockpile of orichalcum.
Am I supposed to know
what that is?
Orichalcum is a power source
that was used in ancient times.
It emits tremendous amounts
of greenhouse gases
that are highly destructive
to our planet.
In fact, we almost destroyed
the oceans ourselves
before we realized
what we were doing.
It can't be disposed of safely,
so the remaining stockpile
has been buried
in 12 storage vaults
deep underground.
We should warn the other places
that are storing the stuff.
He's already been there.
It's all gone.
We think he's been
launching secret raids
for at least five months.
This is just the time
he got caught.
Well, this spike
in global temperatures
that's causing disasters
on the surface
and making
the sea dwellers sick
happened five months ago.
He's using
the stolen orichalcum
to heat the planet.
Why would he do that?
I don't know,
but I'm gonna find out.
If he is using the orichalcum
to heat the planet,
we don't have much time.
He is pushing this
past the tipping point.
He must be stopped
or a global climate meltdown
is imminent.
We need to find him,
but he's completely
vanished off the radar.
I think I know someone
who might be able to help us.
But you're not gonna like it.
Your brother?
Believe me,
he's the last person
I wanna go begging for help,
but he's dealt with Manta
in the past,
and he's the only one who might
know how to find him in time.
The Fishermen will never
allow you to speak to Orm.
He killed their king.
I wasn't exactly
gonna ask for permission.
Arthur, Atlantis cannot extract
Orm from an allied nation.
It would be an act of war.
Atlantis isn't gonna do it.
I'm gonna break him out myself.
Arthur, Karshon is looking
for a reason
to seize war powers.
You will be nothing more than
a figurehead if she does that.
My place is out there
where I belong,
where I'm actually good
at what I do.
I'm tired of nothing
ever getting done.
I've got to do this.
If anyone finds out,
if you're caught...
it will tear
the kingdoms apart.
Then help me not get caught.
Xebelian intelligence
has recently learned
that your brother
is being held
on the surface
in a secret one-of-a-kind
underground facility.
They're assuming
no sea dweller
would ever dare
cross the desert.
And here's a special outfit
for you.
What is that,
boy's extra medium?
It's supposed to be tight.
The chromatophores
change color
and camouflage you
for up to a minute,
making you undetectable
to most sensors.
They'll never see you coming.
What are we doing for comms?
Open comms are too risky.
I'll be sending
a cephalopod with you
to act as a messenger.
That's an octopus.
Tactical Operations
and Pursuit Operative.
Topo, for short.
Genetically
engineered intelligence
for infiltration and espionage.
He also plays a variety
of musical instruments.
Just try and lay low
when we get in there, okay?
You might be invisible,
but your hectocotylus
is starting to smell like
warm chum butter.
Aw, Topo, you dumb squid!
God, come on!
Is ink piss?
The prison is guarded
by fearsome Deserter remnants.
Death-worshipping ascetics
who survived
when the Sahara went dry
by turning to blood
for sustenance.
If they catch you,
they'll bleed you dry.
When you find Orm,
he'll be weak.
They're limiting
his water supply...
just enough
to keep him alive.
And if you do see Orm,
you tell him that I love him.
You tell him
that I think of him every day.
I will.
Look,
I know he's family,
but you can't forget
who you're dealing with here.
Once you've broken Orm out,
you're not gonna be able
to turn your back on him.
You need him,
but you can never trust him.
Whoo... You look rough.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm here to break you out.
Have you lost your mind?
You're the one who put me here.
Eh, why you
bringing up old shit?
- We'll talk about it later.
You cannot break me out.
There's a treaty
with the Fishermen Kingdom.
Look, I gotta stop David Kane
from destroying the world.
And you're the only one
that can help me.
So you do the math.
Oh, shit.
Come on, Cast Away.
Grab Wilson. Let's roll.
- Come on. Let's go.
This changes nothing.
Wouldn't have it any other way,
little brother.
Do not call me "brother."
Hermanito? Come on.
Come on, Topo,
you stupid squid!
Wake up and open the door.
Topo?
The cephalopod?
Trust me, it wasn't my idea.
Topo!
All right, come on.
Wait.
Did you... bring water?
Yeah.
Uh, no, sorry.
I drank it all
on the way here.
- What?
- Bro, it's hot up there.
Whoa! Easy.
- Whoa!
You know how
to ride one of these?
Are you kidding?
I don't even know
what the hell it is.
- Hyaah!
- What?
Yeah!
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, no!
All right,
the water's right there.
Let's go, skinny jeans.
Yeah. All right.
Good job, little brother.
High-five.
No.
All right.
Good job.
You know, I got a bunch
of king shit to do
back in Atlantis
so we should go.
Ahh! Come on, Topo!
This is worse than
I could have possibly imagined.
The safety and security
of Atlantis is a sacred trust.
No king has allowed
the great city wall
to be breached
- in a hundred generations.
A hundred generations? Really?
How many years is that?
I'm bad with geology.
What is that, like,
a million years?
Oh? You're calling me
one in a million?
How can you make jokes
at a time like this?
It's undignified for a king
to jest.
Oh, excuse me, Your Highness,
if I use comedy
to mask my feelings
and deal with stress.
Otherwise,
I'd end up looking like you.
A very tight butthole.
Super tight.
You know,
if the pressures of leadership
are too stressful,
perhaps you should leave
and let someone
who knows what they're doing
be king.
You know what?
I cannot wait to throw your ass
back in prison
when this is all over.
You won't have to.
Once I stop David Kane,
I'll surrender myself
to the Fishermen.
That is my honor to Atlantis.
You're so dramatic.
Whatever.
Just help me find this asshole.
Well, my contact will at least
know where to look.
What happened to him?
David Kane that I knew was
ruthless,
but he wasn't insane.
This guy just put a gun
to the world's head
and pulled the trigger.
Without even making
any demands.
Congratulations, Dr. Shin.
That cannon of yours worked
exactly how you said it would.
Well, you found it.
All I did was figure out
how it worked.
I didn't think we'd
ever actually have to use it
on anyone.
Yeah, well, what can I say?
Things don't always
go as planned.
But that's what I'm afraid of.
David, this stuff
could reshape
the entire planet.
Hey, doc.
We are this close
to unlocking the greatest power
in human history.
Are you really telling me
you want to walk away now?
If I said yes,
would you let me?
Sure.
You want to see how
long you last in that jungle?
Be my guest.
Yeah, I'll stick around.
Yeah.
Welcome to the last frontier.
They scavenged ships
from around the world
to build this place.
The Sunken Citadel.
It is the one place
in the world
where the scum of the land
and sea mingle.
It is where people
come to disappear.
Wow.
It's an impressive shithole.
How have I never
heard of this place before?
It is not meant
to be common knowledge.
It's a pirate haven.
Pirates?
Listen, I don't know
if you know this about me,
but I'm not too popular
with pirates.
Oh, I'm well aware.
Relax. It was the only way
to get us both in.
You could've at least
given me a heads up.
Would you have
gone along with it?
- Hell, no.
- Then put a hook in it.
There. That's Kingfish.
He is the one who put me
in contact with David Kane.
He brokers deals with pirates,
mercenaries, slavers,
you name it.
Cool.
I'm gonna go pick a fight.
Just let me handle this.
He's our best shot
at finding Manta,
and he's not going to tell us
anything if you go in there
flexing your muscles at him.
You're so lucky we didn't grow
up together, little brother.
Do not call me "brother."
Well...
This is a bit of a surprise,
isn't it?
I didn't realize
you'd been released
from prison.
It is a recent development.
Outlaws, aren't we all?
We need to find David Kane.
Bad news, I'm afraid.
David Kane is no longer
on the market.
Not for sale at any price.
He's solely running
as an independent operator.
Where is he holed up now?
In exchange, I offer a favor...
from the King of Atlantis.
You seriously expect me
to play footsie with someone
with that kind of blood
on their hands?
I don't have hands!
Or feet!
Um...
Listen, if the information
checks out good,
I promise you that I won't
immediately come back here
and tear this place apart.
That's too bad.
Traditionally,
the kings of Atlantis
have turned a blind eye
to the Sunken Citadel.
Now, we have to blind it
for you.
Fine. Flex your muscles.
Smash his stupid head in!
Boom!
Gotcha, fatback!
Okay! Okay!
We can work this out. We can.
Talk.
I don't know where he is,
but there have been rumors.
A dormant volcano
in the South Pacific,
called "Devil's Deep."
Talk faster.
It's been barren for years.
But travelers say
there's a jungle there now.
Navigation gets scrambled
as soon as you start
to get close.
And if you get too close,
you don't come back!
If I was a betting man,
and believe me, I am,
I'd say that's where Kane
is hiding out.
We got all we needed. Let's go!
♪ Rise up, come
Rise up through the fire ♪
Soon you'll be
more powerful than he is.
But you're not ready yet,
and you involved him
far too soon.
I sense them closing in on us.
Do I seem concerned?
Hmm?
If anything,
it's even easier now.
We couldn't have planned it
any better than--
Oh. Oh.
Hey.
Uh, I... I just wanted
to tell you
that the orichalcum furnace
is now running at peak output.
I win.
Topo, go back to Atlantis
and give them our coordinates.
You know
what'd be amazing right now?
Reinforcements?
Great, big, greasy cheeseburger
and a pint of Guinness.
You gotta admit, the food
is so much better up here.
I find that hard to believe.
Hold up.
You telling me
you never went topside
to have a cheeseburger?
- What?
- Or a slice of 'za? Pepperoni?
Or a thick, juicy,
medium raw steak
with fries and a shake,
and you dip it--
Even the words
that surface-dwellers
give their food
sound disgusting.
You've let your prejudices
stop you from enjoying
half the world.
You should think about that.
It's your loss, dude.
Aw, yeah!
Bet you never had one of these.
- What is it?
- It's a cockroach.
- You eat it?
- Oh, yeah. Shrimp of the land.
- Mmm. Mmm.
- Eh?
That's good. Here, drink this.
Okay, you first.
Are you seeing this?
That's not normal?
Definitely not normal. Ugh.
Let's get out of here.
You see how dangerous
the orichalcum can be?
I bet it mutated
the flora and fauna
in a short amount of time,
turning them... monstrous.
Whoa.
Oh, shit...
Run!
Come on.
Faster!
What the hell are you doing?
I don't know.
I'm not used to running.
Just do what I do.
Use your arms, use your legs.
Lift them up.
Like this?
- Holy shit.
- Yeah!
- Wait up.
- Whoa!
We have to jump.
We'll survive the fall.
Are you crazy? It's gonna hurt.
What do you wanna do, stay here
and fight the hopping demons?
What is that?
What does that say?
The writing
is ancient Atlantean.
"A true king builds bridges."
What are you doing?
Got any more
krill-brained ideas?
See?
A true king builds bridges.
That's a metaphor!
Hey!
I forgot to tell you.
Mom says she loves you.
She thinks about you
all the time.
Why the hell are you
telling me this now?
I don't know.
I'm just tired of waiting
for the right moment.
Come on.
Looks like my metaphor
just saved your ass.
Uh, David?
I just ran more tests,
and this data
is really disturbing.
We have to stop
burning the... orichalcum.
David?
Oh.
Okay, doc, you want to know
my plan so bad.
Here it is.
I'm gonna kill Aquaman
and destroy everything
he holds dear.
I'm gonna murder his family
and burn his kingdom to ash.
I will avenge my father.
Even if I have to make a deal
with the devil to do it.
David, you can't trust
the trident.
I never draw this blade
unless it's gonna taste blood.
Pray I never show it
to you again.
We must be getting close
to the radiation source.
We should wait
for Atlantis
to receive your message.
We can conduct reconnaissance
in the meantime.
Yeah. Look, Loki,
I'm not asking
for your advice on this.
You've already lived up
to your end of the deal.
So you can go on back
to Azkaban for all I care.
So, what's your plan?
I don't have one, yet.
But he came after my wife,
which means
I'm gonna pull his tongue
out of his butt.
Arthur, you are the king.
You cannot
let this get personal.
This coming from the guy
who turned the entire
nation of Atlantis
into his own private ego trip?
My ego?
You're the one who swam
through the front gate
and challenged my claim
for the throne.
Only because you're trying
to destroy the surface world.
If you weren't such an asshole,
you'd still be king.
Unbelievable.
Wait, wait! Wait!
You took my throne
and you don't even want it?
Are you kidding me?
I hate this job.
Only reason I'm doing it
is to keep Atlantis
from destroying the surface.
And I might even be
screwing that up.
You really
had no ambition for it?
Absolutely not.
From the day
my father found out
you existed,
he prepared me for the moment
that you would come
and challenge me
for the throne.
Wow, that's really sad.
Especially when you think
how easily I kicked your ass
with basically no prep time
whatsoever.
Roasted.
That is not how it happened.
- That's exactly how
it happened.
- Mera saved you.
No, she didn't.
I kicked your ass.
Nope. She made
the little water tornado.
I fell in it.
Okay, shut up.
I think we're here.
Sleep, aloha.
Come on, let's do this.
Once this is over with,
we should go get some
burgers and beers.
- Don't push it.
- Tacos and tequila.
I don't even
know those words.
- Huh?
- Shh!
Hey!
Whoa, brother.
Sasa!
It's an orichalcum furnace.
All that stolen orichalcum.
They're just burning it up.
He's heating
the atmosphere on purpose.
This is catastrophic.
This whole place must
be heat-shielded to protect it
from the surface's
thermal satellites.
Question is,
how do we stop 'em?
To take out this reactor,
we would have to crater
the entire island.
Get away from there! Now!
This blaster may be ancient,
but it was built
for killing Atlanteans.
Okay, I am so sorry.
I did not mean that.
I just didn't want you
to break me in half
before I could surrender.
Please take me with you.
Knock him out and then
help me hide these bodies.
No, no. Wait, please.
I didn't want any of this.
All I wanted
was to see Atlantis
with my own eyes.
I thought I could share
its wonders with the world.
I'm a scientist,
and I just wanted
to be taken seriously.
David Kane said
he could help me,
but now he won't let me leave.
You expect us to believe you
have nothing to do with this?
I know.
I've done things
I'm not proud of.
But he would've killed me
if I hadn't.
Knock him out.
No.
- Then I'll knock him out.
- No!
- What?
- No.
Fine!
You can come with us.
Oh... thank you.
But you better start talking.
Or I'm gonna give you
one sasa!
Okay, okay.
It's the black trident.
It's a direct link
to some ancient evil.
It gives Kane great powers
and in return--
I hate when that happens.
Stop them!
Whoa!
Ow!
No, no, no, no, no!
Not the orichalcum!
You wanna blow us up?
- This stuff blows up?
- Yes!
My bad!
Then stop using it!
Just shut up
and let me save your ass.
Again.
He's going to fight us
without the power suit?
I told you he's stronger now.
He's still
just a surface-dweller.
- Bro!
- Bah!
I never expected to see
you two fighting side by side.
We're making
a special exception
just for you.
No one hits my brother but me.
I was gonna
kill you last,
but thanks for dropping by.
You're making this easy.
Yeah!
Come at me,
the killer of kings.
Take that island down!
Fire at will!
We've got to get out of here.
Malfunction. Malfunction.
Warning. Warning.
Shin, let's go!
What are you waiting for?
Fire the goddamn cannon!
I'm sorry
to drag you all into this.
But the Fishermen can't think
that Atlantis was involved.
Atlantis does not
command the armies of Xebel.
I do.
And the Brine Kingdom
has not forgotten
its debt to you.
You may count on us always.
Something happened to me.
When I touched
that black trident.
Why is he even here?
He should be
on his way back to prison.
We should hear
what he has to say.
I made that mistake once.
That's why I know
he can't be trusted.
And he cut off my claw.
This thing took a whole year
to grow back.
Look, he wants to stop Manta
same as we do.
And just for the record,
the only reason we made it
this far is because of him.
I saw the Lost Kingdom.
Mom, I don't know enough
about this.
Is that even possible?
All anyone knows for sure
is there once
was a seventh kingdom
and then one day,
just before the fall,
every record of it
was stricken
from the chronicles.
How do you know what you saw
was the Lost Kingdom?
No one even knows
what it was called anymore.
It's called Necrus.
And I didn't just see it.
I knew it.
It's almost like I was...
remembering it.
Flashes
of someone else's memories.
During King Atlan's time,
there were
seven united kingdoms
of Atlantis.
And the Black City
was a curse upon them all.
By exploiting orichalcum,
Necrus rapidly became
a superpower unlike any other.
But it came
at a terrible price.
Poisoning the land, the sea,
even the mind of the tyrant
who ruled Necrus.
Atlan's own brother, Kordax.
Atlan pleaded with him
to stop using it
before the world
- was irrevocably damaged.
However,
Kordax resented Atlan,
thinking his own brother
was trying to steal his power.
So, he resorted to dark magic
and crafted
an instrument of evil.
That black trident.
He transformed his people
and himself into monsters...
...to fight Atlantis.
So, the two brothers
went to war.
But Atlan
defeated Kordax
and imprisoned him
and all of Necrus
with a spell cast
with his own blood...
...to ensure
that Kordax's dark power
would never be found.
And that is why
Necrus is stricken
from the chronicles.
This evil was supposed to
remain frozen for eternity.
But David Kane has found it.
And it's slowly possessing him.
But even
with the ice cap melting,
Kordax still can't be freed.
Atlan used blood magic
to seal Kordax in his prison.
Only Atlan himself
could release him.
Manta doesn't need
Atlan himself.
Manta needs Atlan's blood.
Blood magic isn't really magic,
it's DNA.
The key to Kordax's prison
is the royal bloodline itself.
That means he needs blood
from either you, me or Arthur.
We're the end of the bloodline.
No, we're not.
...Wildfires
would have made headlines
across the world,
but now, they're almost
a weekly occurrence.
We're witnessing
unprecedented weather events
across the globe,
and meteorologists
are at a loss
to explain this rapid change
in climate.
From sweltering
heatwaves and droughts,
which are shattering
temperature records,
to torrential rains
and floodings...
- What is going on?
- ...hurricane bearing down
on the East Coast,
leaving one million homes
without power--
Make that a million and one.
I gotta get the flashlight, bubba.
I'm gonna
leave you alive,
so he can watch you die.
Dad!
- Tom!
- Dad!
Tom!
No! Dad!
Where's Junior?
No!
I'm sorry, son.
Where's Junior?
Manta... took Junior.
- No!
No!
The medics have
stabilized his condition.
He will be okay.
We just picked up a signal.
It's faint,
but it's broadcasting
on an old Atlantean
sonar frequency.
Headed to Antarctica.
- Bring our little one back.
- I will.
I've dreamed of this.
The two of you
standing together
as brothers.
Promise me
you will protect each other.
Promise me, Orm.
Go.
Great waves, Nereus.
Your warship is powerful,
but it's slower than a sea cow.
I say we ditch
all this dead weight
and travel light. Hmm?
And what are you gonna do when
he turns on that sonic cannon?
Our only chance is to hit him
with total overwhelming force
from every direction.
Not with Junior
in the crossfire.
What choice do we have?
We have no defense
against that cannon.
Well, wait a minute.
So this cannon
sends out soundwaves
that messes with
our nervous system, right?
That's right.
Ultrasonic echoes.
Well, what if
we disrupt those echoes
with another soundwave
on the same frequency,
but just much, much louder?
You wanna disrupt
their disruption?
Well, that's
gonna be the easy part.
Take your weapons.
And ready your steeds.
Hmm.
Really doesn't like you,
does he?
We made a lot of progress, doc.
They destroyed the furnace
before we could finish the job,
but we were damn close.
One well-placed missile
should do the trick.
My God, what did we do?
Nothing the world
wasn't already doing.
All we did
was fast forward things
a few years.
The ice
hasn't fully melted yet,
but our scanning
reveals a weak spot.
Here.
This will lead you
straight to Kordax.
Power up the sonic cannon.
Bag the child and suit up.
- Yah!
Captain, we have
multiple incoming hostiles.
You're too late.
No.
Commence charge.
You've got to be kidding me.
Astounding.
This place is immense.
It could be anywhere.
The throne of Necrus
is in the heart of the city.
I sense something
in the water.
Everyone, light it up.
Didn't you say that Kordax
turned his people
into an army of monsters?
Yes. I did.
Keep your eyes open.
Well, that'll be easy.
Mine don't close.
Everyone stand ready.
Something's coming.
Fire at will!
I think this goes
all the way through.
My men and I can deal
with these worms.
Go now and save the prince.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Come on, you spineless worms!
Bring it on!
Help me!
Give me the child.
You picked the wrong day
to grow a spine, doc.
Get behind
the portcullis!
We need to close the gate!
Get away from my son!
Your blood
will do just fine.
You want blood? Come get it!
Aquaman!
Oh!
You wear
my brother's armor,
and wield his trident,
but you're only
half the man he was.
How pathetic.
Mera!
Go!
Mera...
Run!
Free me
from my prison,
and all my power
will be yours
to wield as you desire.
Kill him,
and you will be
Ocean Master again!
Well, now
this is certainly
an improvement.
Powerful, Atlantean body.
And this one hates you more
than the other one did.
It's not true.
Come on, little brother.
I know you're in there.
Don't you see?
You can't win.
Either you kill your brother
or you die.
By an Atlan's blood,
this magic is broken.
My eternal night
is ending.
I'm done fighting your puppets,
Kordax.
I'm coming for you.
- Give it to me!
- No!
I can end this.
Don't let him take it!
Hasn't he taken enough already?
Yield the throne.
It's time for me
to reclaim my destiny.
It would be foolish
to think he could ever change.
I knew you would do this.
You are the one true king.
Atlantis deserves
its one true king.
I am the one true king!
You know, there was a time
when I wanted
to meet you more than anything.
Let you know
that you weren't alone,
that we were in it together.
Promise me
you'll protect each other.
Come on, little brother,
let's end this bastard.
I meant what I said
when I first met you.
No matter what,
you are not alone.
We're in this together.
You are my brother.
Orm.
Let go.
Orm, let it go.
I live again!
I have waited
countless centuries
in the dark
for this moment.
Shit.
Arthur!
Never.
Arthur, we've gotta go.
The magic is broken.
Let's get outta here!
Hurry!
That's right!
Come on, baby! Yeah!
Yeah!
My love.
- Hi, baby boy.
Shin.
Thank you.
Astounding.
All here looking intact.
That's good. That's good.
Well, I'm not.
My claw got cut off.
Again!
You're one tough crustacean,
Your Highness.
Bah!
As far as I'm concerned,
your debt is paid.
Not everybody's gonna see it
that way though.
It's too bad you went
and had yourself killed
back there.
Yes.
All this ice.
It'd be impossible
to find the body.
Just lay low
for a while.
But don't go too far.
I may need to call you up
for some advice.
You know, with the whole
running the kingdom thing.
Thank you...
brother.
You're not as bad at this
as you think.
The people of Atlantis
are lucky to have you.
You are everything I was not.
You do the right thing
when doing the wrong
thing is much easier.
And you're willing
to ask for help
even from your worst enemy.
I know it may not feel like
you know what you're
doing sometimes, but...
keep trusting your instincts.
If you lead,
Atlantis will follow.
After all, a true king
builds bridges, right?
I thought that was just
a metaphor.
Well, your metaphor
might have just saved
the world's ass.
We've got breaking news.
We are witnessing history.
A moment the ramifications
of which simply...
cannot be overstated.
A first contact...
...with the undersea nation
of Atlantis.
An entire civilization hidden
for thousands of years
about to be revealed.
I think it's safe to say
the world
will never be the same.
The King of Atlantis
has reached out
to the United Nations
and will be officially
seeking membership.
And is expected
to propose a joint effort
to reverse the climate issues.
We are
told that this was the result
of weeks of secret negotiations
with the United Nations.
We now go live to Ellis Island,
where the first official
ambassador from Atlantis
is about to address
the United Nations.
I come here today as
a representative of two worlds.
The land and the sea.
And I stand here as proof
that change is coming to both.
And I'm calling
for global unity
for a global crisis.
To finally bring harmony
between us
and the natural balance
of our world.
Atlantis stands ready
to help contribute
its science and technology.
And with your
knowledge of the air,
and our knowledge of the seas,
together we can write
the next chapter in our story,
rather than its ending.
Sometimes it's gonna seem
like our differences
are too extreme,
but all we have to do
is look beneath the surface,
to see that we're
all here on this planet
with the same goals
and aspirations.
- Even when our customs...
- Here you go.
...might seem strange
and unfamiliar.
Beer and a cheeseburger.
Extra greasy
like you asked for.
And by
overcoming our prejudices,
we'll become stronger and
learn more about ourselves.
We can seize this moment
to create a better
more hopeful future,
for our children,
and our families.
My name is Arthur Curry.
I'm the rightful sovereign
of the undersea nation
of Atlantis.
I'm a father, a brother,
a warrior and a friend.
I'm the King of Atlantis.
I am Aquaman.
♪ Get your motor runnin' ♪
♪ Head out on the highway ♪
♪ Looking for adventure ♪
♪ In whatever comes our way ♪
♪ Yeah, darlin'
Go and make it happen ♪
♪ Take the world
In a love embrace ♪
♪ Fire all of your guns
At once ♪
♪ And explode into space ♪
♪ Space, space ♪
♪ I like smoke and lightnin' ♪
♪ Heavy metal thunder ♪
♪ Racing with the wind ♪
♪ And the feeling
That I'm under ♪
♪ Yeah, darlin'
Go and make it happen ♪
♪ Take the world
In a love embrace ♪
♪ Fire all of your guns
At once ♪
♪ And explode into space ♪
♪ Like a true nature's child ♪
♪ We were born
Born to be wild ♪
♪ We can climb so high ♪
♪ I never wanna die ♪
♪ Born to be wild ♪
♪ Get your motor runnin' ♪
♪ Head out on the highway ♪
♪ Looking for adventure ♪
♪ In whatever comes our way ♪
♪ Yeah, darlin'
Go and make it happen ♪
♪ Take the world
In a love embrace ♪
♪ Fire all of your guns
At once ♪
♪ And explode into space ♪
♪ Like a true nature's child ♪
♪ We were born
Born to be wild ♪
♪ We can climb so high ♪
♪ I never wanna die ♪
♪ Born to be wild ♪
Mmm.
♪ When your fire burns out ♪
♪ Shine a light
Through the clouds ♪
♪ When you need a friend ♪
♪ If you sink or swim
I'll follow you off
Of the deep end ♪
♪ I'll follow you off
♪ Sink or swim
I'll follow you off of the ♪
♪ Pressure cooker
Everybody's watching
Your every move ♪
♪ Every move ♪
♪ You're claustrophobic
Fear the future
Fear for your every move ♪
♪ Every move ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Stuck in your personal hell ♪
♪ I'll meet you down there
Myself ♪
♪ When your fire burns out ♪
♪ Shine a light
Through the clouds ♪
♪ When you need a friend ♪
♪ If you sink or swim
I'll follow you off
Of the deep end ♪
♪ I'll follow you off
♪ Sink or swim
I'll follow you off of the-- ♪
♪ Fight the fever
Tryna burn out the darkness ♪
♪ Whatever it takes
Whatever it takes ♪
♪ Head underwater
You can ride out the wave ♪
♪ Until it breaks
Whatever it takes ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Stuck in your personal hell ♪
♪ I'll meet you down there
Myself ♪
♪ When your fire burns out ♪
♪ Shine a light
Through the clouds ♪
♪ When you need a friend ♪
♪ If you sink or swim
I'll follow you off
Of the deep end ♪
♪ I'll follow you off
♪ Sink or swim
I'll follow you off
Of the deep end ♪
Downloaded from YTS.MX
Modify by Blue-Bird™